<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.program.xcloud" name="X-Cloud Dev" version="2.6.1" provider-name="Xeno-Gaming">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.9"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <disclaimer>For X-Cloud</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="de">Beliebige Anwendungen aus X-Cloud starten.</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Start any applications from X-Cloud.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Lancer n'importer quelle application depuis X-Cloud.</summary>
        <summary lang="fi">Käynnistää sovelluksia X-Cloud:stä</summary>
        <description lang="de">X-Cloud Dev erlaubt das Starten beliebiger Linux, Windows und OS X Anwendungen (mit oder ohne Kommandozeile) direkt aus der X-Cloud Oberfläche. X-Cloud Dev erlaubt weiterhin das Editieren, Herunterladen und Verwalten der Metadaten (Informationen und Bilder) für diese Anwendungen aus dem Internet.</description>
        <description lang="en">X-Cloud Dev allows you to start any Linux, Windows and OS X applications (with command line support or not) directly from the X-Cloud GUI. X-Cloud Dev also give you the possibility to edit, download (from Internet resources) and manage all the meta-data (informations and images) related to these applications.</description>
	<description lang="ru">X-Cloud Dev позволяет запускать любые приложения Linux, Windows и OS X (с поддержкой командной строки или нет) непосредственно из Коди GUI. X-Cloud Dev также даст вам возможность редактировать, загружать (из интернет-ресурсов) и управлять всеми мета-данными (информация и изображения), связанными с этими приложениями.</description>
        <description lang="fr">X-Cloud Dev permet de lancer toutes les applications Linux, Windows and OS X (avec support des lignes de commandes ou non) directement depuis l'interface de X-Cloud. X-Cloud Dev offre également la possibilité de modifier, télécharger (depuis les ressoures web) et de gérer toues les meta-donées (informations et images) relatives à ces applications.</description>
        <description lang="fi">X-Cloud Devilla voit käynnistää X-Cloud:n käyttöliittymästä mitä tahansa sovelluksia. Käynnistettävistä sovelluksista voi hakea tietoja ja kuvia Internet-tietokannoista.</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
